What is this?
A peace offering.
What do you mean?
The white flag of surrender raised by the other side.
How dare he fake illness to trick me.
But considering he took the initiative to make peace,
I'll reluctantly forgive him.
It seems you've got the primary and secondary conflicts
mixed up.
What?
The reason you were angry before
was jealousy, not faking illness,
right?
This doesn't count as jealousy.
I just can't stand seeing his pathetic face
when he flatters my sister.
But now I know the reason.
Then
just forgive him.
For what reason?
Why are you still reading manga at your age?
Only boring adults would think that way.
My ex used to say the same thing.
It made it so I couldn't even read it openly.
But before today,
you never read it in front of me either.
Right. In the past,
I read it secretly.
However, you've passed my best friend test.
From today on, I'm going to read it freely in front of you,
until the end of the world.
When did I pass?
I don't know.
Actually, many things
happen imperceptibly and then burst out.
Is that from this manga too?
Let me see.
It's good, right?
Is it?
This big-nosed moon.
What's wrong?
Don't you think a friend who randomly distances herself from you,
and then tricks you
into getting a shot because you faked an illness
is going a bit too far?
Such a long, thick needle.
Is it that hard to admit you like her?
To tell you the truth,
I've tailored a
cruel revenge plan just for her.
Is it that hard to answer my question directly?
I'm going to give her a taste of her own medicine.
These next few days,
I'll give her the cold shoulder
so she knows what it feels like to be treated hot and cold.
Deliberately distancing yourself
to test your place in her heart.
Nonsense.
Spot on.
It's just you and me here.
No third person will know
that you like Li Xinyue.
What?
You like Li Xinyue?
I...
Why are you here?
I've been here the whole time.
You two were so engrossed in your chat,
so I didn't interrupt.
We absolutely can't let a fourth person know.
Why does this sound so familiar?
Don't worry, you two.
My lips are sealed.
Sister Yiying.
I have an explosive secret.
That Zhang Yang,
he likes...
I know.
Aren't you surprised?
Why can't I feel the joy
of sharing gossip with you?
Look.
Zhang Yang, Tang Yi, Sister Yiying, Lin Yiyi.
I know.
Should I just tell Li Xinyue directly?
Are you stupid? She already knows.
Here you go.
The Cai family's ancient residential complex
was built by Cai Qichang, an overseas Chinese in the Philippines.
It was mainly built by Cai Zishen and his son.
Construction started with land purchase in 1855
and was completed in 1911.
It eventually formed this entire residential complex before your eyes,
known as the 'Little Forbidden City of Southern Fujian'
and the 'Grand View Garden of Southern Fujian Architecture'.
This is the whole building complex.
Stop.
Don't think you can just read the script because your Mandarin is standard.
It gives me a headache.
Is it wrong to speak standard Mandarin?
Of course not.
You are not arguing with me today.
Your happiness is the most important.
What's going on?
Zhang Yang.
I was wrong about what happened last time.
I apologize to you.
Li Xinyue.
It is work time now.
Okay.
This skydiving is so thrilling.
Just watching it is awesome.
You're just watching.
Would you actually dare to go?
If you don't do exciting things when you're young,
it'll be so boring when you're too old for it.
Kids these days are little terrors.
Who is it?
Our little client.
Probably a rebellious phase.
That's normal.
Kids at this age,
the more serious you act, the more annoyed she gets.
You need to do something special.
Something special?
For example?
Like taking her to do something thrilling.
Thrilling?
According to statistics,
seeking high-intensity sensory stimulation.
It is most common in adolescence and early adulthood.
This is part of their psychological development
and their search for self-identity.
Stop talking nonsense.
Well said.
Go on.
When they are 13 or 14 years old,
they like things that look dangerous,
exciting, and fun.
Can you stop coming up with bad ideas?
Good idea.
Dangerous and fun,
and exciting.
I think.
I got it.
No way.
Yang,
welcome to Qingjing Taoyuan.
Look,
we have a lot of thrilling activities here.
Thrilling, huh?
Over there,
there's a 98-meter glass skywalk.
And here, look.
Warrior roller coaster.
Mongolian archery.
How about it? Anything you're interested in?
I don't think she's interested at all.
Why don't we choose something
a bit more approachable?
Who said I'm not interested?
How is it?
It looks good, right?
It's a great spot for taking photos.
Let me take a picture for you.
We have professional photographers.
They take great photos.
Photographer!
It's okay, I'll take it with my phone.
Phone cameras are pretty good too.
You are very noisy. Let me be alone for a while,
okay?
Okay.
If you need anything later,
contact me anytime.
I will keep my line open.
Zhang Yang.
Don't you feel that when you run,
the bridge is moving?
Mr. Zhang.
Well, not only are you afraid of the dark,
you are also afraid of heights, right?
No.
The weather is nice today.
The weather is quite good.
But,
are you afraid of all
the thrilling rides?
Do we have a grudge?
Being polite,
only talking about work,
never crossing the line,
following all your instructions.
How does that displease you?
Anyway, you did it on purpose.
You don't seem to like
being treated politely by me.
Why is that?
Then tell me
your reason for intentionally ignoring me.
I am wrongly accused, your honor.
I have always been diligent and hardworking.
It is just human nature.
How could it be on purpose?
Slow down.
You... you...
Have you ever seen 'Final Destination'?
There's a bridge exactly like this in it.
I have. It's fine, let's go.
Just move your legs.
Hurry up.
What I recommend most is this Warrior Roller Coaster.
It is currently the longest, highest,
and steepest tubular slide in Fujian Province.
How is it?
How about we choose something else?
Letting a kid sit there,
what if she cries?
Does she look scared to you?
No, what if she cries,
what do we do if we get a complaint?
She won't be scared.
You have to think, if she complains about us...
You like her, and she likes you.
Why are you arguing here?
Ready? We're about to start.
Ready, ready.
Ready.
Hurry. Hold on to me if you're scared later.
Really?
You won't be.
It's very slow. Look at it.
Come on, fasten your seatbelts.
It's fine.
How is it? Are you feeling happier?
I don't like traveling at all.
Why?
Slow down.
Hello. Can I pet him?
Sure.
What's his name?
His name is Doudou.
Doudou.
How old is he?
Two years old.
You are two years old, Doudou.
So cute.
Come, Doudou,
say goodbye to the sisters.
Bye-bye, Doudou.
Let's go.
It seems you really like small animals.
Liking them isn't necessarily a good thing.
What do you mean?
Whenever something you like leaves you,
you will be very sad.
How do you know so much at such a young age?
I'm not young.
I don't think I'll live past 18.
I thought the same way when I was your age.
But when you grow up a little more,
and see more of the world,
you'll find out.
This world is quite interesting.
That's because you're in love.
But you're different from them.
You don't lecture me.
Can we be friends?
Of course. We are good friends now.